<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns:yt="http://www.youtube.com/xml/schemas/2015" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw"/>
 <id>yt:channel:UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</id>
 <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
 <title>Get The Gloss</title>
 <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw"/>
 <author>
  <name>Get The Gloss</name>
  <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
 </author>
 <published>2012-01-27T11:24:35+00:00</published>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:oqV4DS-gRIs</id>
  <yt:videoId>oqV4DS-gRIs</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>How to do the Curly Flick | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oqV4DS-gRIs"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2017-02-20T09:39:49+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-03-01T03:11:25+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How to do the Curly Flick | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/oqV4DS-gRIs?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/oqV4DS-gRIs/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>The Curly Flick
 
Produced in partnership with Sassoon
 
Curls are back, but there’s a knack to turning straight hair into real-looking, bouncing waves. We teamed up with the experts at Sassoon to show us how.
 
SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv 
 
Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com
 
Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss
 
 
First, start by applying Sassoon Professional Curl Form hair mousse to hair to add hold and texture, then blow dry smooth. Massage the roots to add volume. Next take a long lasting hair spray such as Sassoon Professional’s Edit Hold Hairspray and spray each section of hair thoroughly.
 
Next, taking small sections of the hair, wrap around a small tong, making sure the ends are left out to give a natural finish. Repeat all around the head, alternating between a medium and a small tong.
 
On top of the head, part hair over to one side and pin out of the way as you continue to tong the hair. Make sure the curls tumble to one side, and once done leave hair until it’s cold to the touch. Once set, tip head forward and massage roots to add volume. Flip hair back and pull through the curls with your fingers rather than a brush which would pull the curl out. Flip hair over to one side and spray with a dry shampoo such as Sassoon Professional’s Illuminating Clean Shampoo to add more texture. Finish with Sassoon Edit Hold hairspray to set in place.
 
Hair by Sassoon
Direction: Susannah Taylor
Model:  Amanda Urvall Nyren
Makeup: Neil Young at Premier Hair and Makeup</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="120" average="4.80" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2832"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:DHpbWqhLDoM</id>
  <yt:videoId>DHpbWqhLDoM</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Straight hair four ways | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DHpbWqhLDoM"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2017-02-14T15:26:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-28T05:07:03+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Straight hair four ways | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/DHpbWqhLDoM?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/DHpbWqhLDoM/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Produced in partnership with Sassoon

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv 

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:

TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Whether you were born with naturally straight hair or would like to tap into this season's trend for super smooth, glossy locks, we have worked here with Sassoon to style straight hair in four very different ways. Here's how to recreate the look:
 
First, to prep the hair, dampen hair with a conditioning spray as Sassoon's Halo Hydrate Leave-in conditioner (http://www.sassoon-salon.com/en/salon/uk/salons). If your hair is particularly wild, use a blow dry spray instead. Using a flat brush, blow-dry hair away from the face. Section the top of the hair off and pin out of the way. Then, using a dense bristle brush,  blow-dry hair bit by bit, keeping the nozzle on the hairdryer and pointing it down the shaft of the hair.  Don't use straightening irons as this knocks the life out of the hair. Blast cold air through all the sections to lock in shine and set the hair smooth.
 
Next, spray a bristle brush with Sassoon Edit Hold Re workable long lasting hairspray and brush through the hair line to tend to any flyaways or frizz. 
 
Look 1 - Simply Straight
Using a pintail comb to create a sharp line, centre part the hair. Leave hair as is.
 
Look 2 - The Low Pony
Using a hair bungee, tie hair in a low ponytail, just away from the nape of the neck. Finish with Sassoon Edit Hold Long-Lasting Finish Spray
 
Look 3 - The Half Up-do
Take a section from above each ear and tether at the back with an invisible band. Add a decorative click and set with hairspray
 
Look 4 - The Side-Slick
Using the pintail comb again, part the hair, lining it up with the corner of your eyebrow. Spray a bristle brush with Sassoon's Edit Hold Reworkable Long lasting finishing spray and brush through. Add hair jewels to the side with the parting such as these beautiful constellation ones from Anthropologie. Bring the opposite side of hair forwards to frame your face.

 
Director - Susannah Taylor
Film by Lock Studios
Hair by Bruce Masefield
Model  - Amanda Urvall Nyren
Makeup Neil Young at Premier Hair and Makeup
Dress from Anthropologie
Feather and star hair clips from Anthropologie</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="124" average="4.90" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2684"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:yU85vCU3s2E</id>
  <yt:videoId>yU85vCU3s2E</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>The Modern Blowdry | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yU85vCU3s2E"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2017-02-07T14:53:59+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-03-01T02:28:10+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The Modern Blowdry | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/yU85vCU3s2E?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/yU85vCU3s2E/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Produced in partnership with Sassoon

There are blow-dries and then there are blow-dries. We have teamed up with Sassoon to show you how to get the perfect salon finish at home.

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_c...

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

How many times have you come home from a salon and wished you could blow-dry your hair like they do? Well we have teamed up with the super stylists at Sassoon and they have shown us how to create the perfect blow-dry that lasts.

Firstly Spritz hair using a conditioning spray such as Sassoon Professional Halo Hydrate, then using a decent sized ball of Sassoon Professional Body Hold Mousse, coat every strand. Brush through using a paddle brush.

Next, using a long toothed brush,  rough dry the hair, lifting at the roots before adding a nozzle to then control air flow. Using a smoothing brush, then section hair off, and pointing the nozzle down the hair shaft, blow-dry hair smooth bit by bit. 

After completing a piece (and whilst still hot) then roll each section into a large pin curl before pinning with a section clip. Whilst each section sets, continue to blow-dry and pin curl the rest of the hair, always making sure the hair rolls under, not up.

Leave the hair to set for 10 minutes and set with Sassoon Professional Edit Hold Finishing Spray 
 After ten minutes, remove the section clips and spray again. Throw the head forward and massage at the roots and pull each curl through with fingers (do not brush). Sweep the front section back from the face and set with hairspray once more.

For Sassoon products go to http://www.sassoon-salon.com/en/salon/uk/salons

Director: Susannah Taylor

Film by Lock Studios

Hair by Sassoon

Model:- Amanda Urvall Nyren

Makeup by Neil Young at Premier Hair and Makeup

Dress from Anthropologie.com</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="141" average="3.61" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4661"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:Y5OBFlIfOUc</id>
  <yt:videoId>Y5OBFlIfOUc</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Rosie Huntington-Whiteley Talks Beauty &amp; Health with Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y5OBFlIfOUc"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2017-02-06T16:45:35+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-03-01T11:22:31+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Rosie Huntington-Whiteley Talks Beauty &amp; Health with Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Y5OBFlIfOUc?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/Y5OBFlIfOUc/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>23 Quick-fire questions on what it takes to be a supermodel

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_c...

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Who doesn't have a girl crush on Rosie Huntington-Whiteley? Here she spills all her supermodel secrets from what she'd rustle up for a quick dinner for us all to her biggest beauty mishap and which type of exercise she does weekly. 

1.  Lip Gloss or Lipstick?
Rosie says  &quot;Lipstick because it's more versatile.&quot;

2.  Warrior Pose or HIIT workout?
Rosie explains she does both -  hard exercise 3/4 times a week and yoga a few times too

3.Most cherished piece of clothing?
Rosie says a pair of Paige denim skinny jeans she's owned for 8 years.

4. When did you last laugh until you cried?
Rosie says when she was with her brother at Christmas when he was telling her a very amusing story.

5. What is your favourite eye product?
Rosie loves her Creme Eyeshadow sticks from Rosie For Autograph because they are easy, buildable and very blendable (http://bit.ly/2lbt0YD)

6. What's your favourite lip product?
&quot;I'm all about the three new lipsticks we are launching this spring,&quot; says Rosie. &quot;They are intense, bold colours.&quot;

7. What do you do if you need to look wide awake in 5 minutes flat but are really tired or jet lagged?
Rosie says she would wash her face, brush her teeth, use eyedrops, curl her eyelashes, conceal any blemishes and scrape her hair back before running out the door.

8. Favourite music to workout to?
To workout Rosie listens to her trainer Simone de La Roux's playlist on Spotify which is very high energy. To relax she listens to The XX, London Grammar and Classical music (although worries that makes her sound old!).

8. What's your worst beauty mishap?
Rosie describes a terrible time when her whole body was cast for a film of Mad Max and they put paper mache all over her. When they moulded her head and pulled it off it ripped all her eyelashes out. Ouch.

9.What is your guilty food pleasure?
Rosie says french fries, fried food, fish 'n' chips, a Sunday roast, or a burger. &quot;I love my food&quot; she says. 

10. What are the three things you keep in your fridge?
'Eggs, milk and a bit of cheese,&quot; says Rosie, oh and some tomatoes. &quot;If you can make an omelette you will never go hungry,&quot; she laughs.

11. How do you style your hair yourself?
Rosie washes her hair then gets a big round brush to smooth it out, then tongs her hair to give a tousled finish.

12. What skincare product would you cry about if you lost?
Rosie says she can't live without IS Clinicals Active Serum which is great for combination skin. She also adores her new Sheer Finish Complexion Enhancer from Rosie for Autograph.

13. Who do you think has great beauty style  - either present or deceased?
Rosie really admires Elizabeth Taylor for her screen siren beauty but also Diane Kruger who she feels is really well put together.

14. How do you motivate yourself to workout if you really don't want to?
Rosie says you should listen to your body and if you are having one of those days then maybe don't do it. She also says some days you just need a kick up the butt though. 'Remember how you are going to feel at the end of it' she insists.

15. What would you make us for lunch if we came over?
Rosie says she'd make a healthy, simple salad and nice piece of chicken or fish.

16. What is your favourite cocktail?
A martini -  dirty, espresso or lychee flavoured are top of her list.

17. Leave a spot or squeeze a spot?
Squeeze she says! &quot;There is no way I'm leaving a whitehead on my face,&quot; she squeals.

18. What are your 3 top travel must-haves?
Rosie says a lint roller, some dry shampoo, a hairbrush and her 'Five minute face', her Amazing radiance Cream (http://bit.ly/2kdOVKJ), Blusher (http://bit.ly/2lbuUZb) and some her Rosie for Autograph Bronzer (http://bit.ly/24ZQzCg).

19. Town or country?
Rosie is a country girl at heart as she grew up in Devon but knows she has to work in the city. She likes a mix of both.

20. Desert Island Dish?
If she could have one meal, Rosie's would be roast chicken with all the trimmings.

21. What 's the weirdest thing you've ever heard about yourself?
Rosie says she can't really think of anything as she doesn't pay too much attention to that sort of thing.

22. What's something that many people don't know about you?
Rosie studied Japanese for 5 years and goes on to speak a bit.

23. What's the one thing you can't live without?
Rightly, Rosie says 'Love'.

Rosie's latest makeup collection for Autograph at M&amp;S can be found at http://bit.ly/2lgsDJ9

Filming by Pocketmotionpictures.com</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="211" average="4.75" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="10456"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:m5Vgpq64U7I</id>
  <yt:videoId>m5Vgpq64U7I</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>How to do the plaited chignon | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m5Vgpq64U7I"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-12-21T18:27:21+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-22T07:35:03+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>How to do the plaited chignon | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/m5Vgpq64U7I?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/m5Vgpq64U7I/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Produced in partnership with Sassoon

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv 

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:

TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

The plaited chignon is a modern take on the traditional up-do and is perfect for the party season or any event where you feel you need something extra special. Sassoon have worked with us to bring us this modern, romantic hair video. Here's how to recreate the look: 

First, dampen dry hair with Sassoon's Halo Hydrate Leave-in conditioner, £18.50 (http://bit.ly/2i8UrO3) spritzing it throughout. Then, taking a bristle brush blow dry the hairline smooth leaving the rest with its natural texture. If your hair is prone to being super straight then do as Sassoon have done and spray thoroughly with dry shampoo such as EiMi Dry Me Dry Shampoo, £8.90 (http://bit.ly/2hZqu3t) before rough drying the hair away from the face.  

Next, using your hands, pull hair into a ponytail without smoothing hair too much and leaving some tendrils out.  Secure with a hair bungee at the nape of the neck. Then divide hair into four plaits (it doesn't matter if they are not all the same size), and tie each with an invisible band. Then, using kirby grips a similar colour to your hair, wrap the plaits around themselves to make a ball shape, pinning the ends in as you go. Once complete, spray with Sassoon Edit Hold Long-lasting Finish Spray, £15.70 (http://bit.ly/2i8UrO3). Refine the shape using your hands.

Leave the look as is or, taking a length of ribbon, tie it around the head tying in a bow behind one ear.

Director: Susannah Taylor

Film by Lock Studios

Hair by Sassoon

Model:- Amanda Urvall Nyren

Makeup by Neil Young at Premier Hair and Makeup

Dress: Rebecca Valance from Netaporter.com</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="112" average="4.54" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3302"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:N2ZiE09I8ys</id>
  <yt:videoId>N2ZiE09I8ys</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Getting rid of spots (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N2ZiE09I8ys"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-12-20T12:42:48+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-18T08:20:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Getting rid of spots (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/N2ZiE09I8ys?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/N2ZiE09I8ys/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks about a problem she has been having with her skin and what she's done to combat it 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Recently, Susannah broke out in a lot of very tiny spots. Frustrated and concerned, she went straight to a specialist. As she notes, there’s no point in trying to tackle it with over-the-counter or our bathroom cabinet products if you’re not sure that they are actually going to work. 

Susannah went to see dermatologist, Dr Sam Bunting, who had helped many of her friends with their skin problems. Susannah firmly believes that if you want results, you need to see an expert – which will speed everything up.

Dr Bunting told Susannah to stop worrying about her skin problem being hormonal, as it was actually down to the use of too many products. Susannah notes that she’s surprised this hasn’t actually happened before as she is always trying out new products for her job. 

Susannah has had to go back to basics with her skincare regime and stick to really good, but basic products that are dermatologically tested and made for sensitive skin, as her skin was so inflamed. 

Susannah started the regime with the La Roche-Posay Toleriane Dermo-Cleanser, £8.30 (http://bit.ly/2huXKPp) to remove her makeup and cleanse morning and night. It’s perfect for anyone with skin that has become inflamed and irritated. It contains no perfume, preservatives, alcohol or colour. Although it is a great product, Susannah does miss using her regular products with their beautiful scents. 

Next, Susannah has been using the Finacea 15% Gel. It contains 15% azelaic acid, a naturally occurring acid, which helps calm inflamed skin and zap the bacteria that acne breeds on. It also exfoliates the dead skin cells to minimise build-up on the skin. Application must be gradual, as it can sting a little at first. Start by using it every other day and building it up to everyday use. 

Susannah has been using the Avene Skin Recovery Cream, £16.50 (http://buff.ly/2gKKU13) for dry, hypersensitive and irritable skin. It is non-comedogenic, and so wont block pores, hypoallergenic and fragrance-free too. It looks after your skin and brings it back to its natural balance.

When out in the sun, Susannah has been using the Neostrata Sheer Physical Protection, £30 (http://buff.ly/2hElnrR). It has broad-spectrum coverage and is SPF50. Neostrata is a highly effective brand and this SPF is very sheer and light and sinks quickly into the skin. 

After a month of using these products, Susannah’s skin has cleared up. Although she was prescribed antibiotics, Susannah opted for a change in skincare regime - and it has worked a treat.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="61" average="4.93" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="2890"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:ua8PQtOKlRE</id>
  <yt:videoId>ua8PQtOKlRE</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>What I want for Christmas (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ua8PQtOKlRE"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-12-15T16:40:10+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-01-27T08:03:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>What I want for Christmas (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/ua8PQtOKlRE?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/ua8PQtOKlRE/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor chats to us about what she would love to find under the tree this Christmas 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Firstly, Susannah has been lusting after the Hourglass Illume Sheer Colour Trio, £56 (http://bit.ly/2huW60a). Susannah loves a beauty product that can give her a glow and this does just that. It features a cream highlighter, cream blusher and cream bronzer and from previous experience from similar products in the Hourglass range, Susannah notes that this will give a beautiful finish to the skin that give a post-holiday effect.  

To stash her pens or paint brushes, Susannah would love to find the Pentreath Hall Alphabet Brush Pot, £40 (http://buff.ly/2hsG5ul) under the tree this year. It’s a crystal tumbler that has been coloured and Susannah absolutely adores it. 

Even though Susannah gets a lot of beauty products to try for work, there are some products that really stand out and the Charlotte Tilbury Magic Cream, £70 (http://bit.ly/2hl6FoE) is one of them. This hydrator containing SPF15, camellia oil, rosewater and aloe vera creates a beautiful and luminous glow without a greasy finish. Susannah notes that when she had a pot she saved it for special occasions, as she loved it so much and would love to welcome it back into her beauty regime. 

After discovering the Anthropologie Constellation Bobby Set, £32 (http://buff.ly/2gZJQ70) on a shoot recently, Susannah would love a set for herself. She would love to get on board with the hair jewel trend with these constellation inspired, vintage-looking hair accessories.  

In this digital age, Susannah loves to write hand written cards as its super personal and she is desperate to get her hands on some personalised stationary to do this with. The personalised note cards from papier.com is what Susannah has her eye on and the Papier Ludo Pink Stationary Set by Luke Edward Hall, from £0.90 (http://buff.ly/2gZIqti) is at the top of Susannah’s list. With the opportunity to include your name at the top, Susannah notes that this would make her incredibly happy each time she wrote on them. 

Susannah has been looking for a long, cross the shoulder bag and the J Crew Mini Rider Bag In Italian Leather, £98 (http://buff.ly/2gZLdCI) is the one she is lusting after. She would love to use it at the weekend in contrast to her bigger bag for the week, which is usually filled to the brim with her laptop and more. 

Sticking to J Crew, the next thing on Susannah’s list comes from their jewellery section. Susannah notes that J Crew do incredible costume jewellery that looks a lot more expensive than it is (linked here http://buff.ly/2hEqSHl)

Finally, to add to Susannah’s candle obsession, she would love to find the Diptyque Le roi Sapin Candle, £48 (http://buff.ly/2gZKvW8) under the tree this year. Part of the holiday collection this year, it contains fig, resin, cedar and patchouli and has an older scent to it.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="62" average="4.74" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1810"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:wleBc1CneMo</id>
  <yt:videoId>wleBc1CneMo</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>The best budget buys of the season (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wleBc1CneMo"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-12-05T14:31:19+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-28T00:25:50+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>The best budget buys of the season (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/wleBc1CneMo?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/wleBc1CneMo/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks us through the best budget beauty products this season

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

The Rimmel InstaFlawless Primer, £6.99 (http://bit.ly/2h9J8Ik) is a tinted primer that has a slight coverage to it and gives skin a tinted glow. Although this product calls itself a primer, it works well on its own as it is very similar to a BB cream, notes Susannah. She often favours a lighter foundation, as she hates it when it totally masks her skin. For her, this primer is the perfect solution. 

If you are looking for a fuller base coverage, Susannah recommends the Revlon ColourStay 2 in 1 Compact Makeup and Concealer, £13.99 (http://buff.ly/2h9HbM1). It is great for covering up blemishes and imperfections and gives skin a flawless finish. The sponge included in the compact navigates all the indents of the face with ease and the concealer can be easily blended on top for added coverage.

Susannah absolutely loves the Models Own Gilt 3 in 1 Eyes, Lips and Face Palette, £19.99 (http://buff.ly/2gaVVIt)  right now. The price may seem high for a budget recommendation but you get a great deal for your money. The beautiful rose gold palette features four eye shadows (two neutral pink-toned matte shades and two bronze/copper-toned shades), two natural lip colours and a beautiful peachy coral blush. The pigment density in the blush is impressive; a little goes a long way. The eye shadows blend well and work both for day and night. Susannah notes that while do-it-all palettes usually cost a lot more from higher end brands - this one really is just as good. 

For mascara, Susannah recommends the L’Oreal Paris False Lash Sculpt Mascara, £9.99 (http://bit.ly/2gXL5EJ). It has a fine plastic comb with shallow plastic teeth in place of a brush. The comb gets right to the base of the lashes to lift while combing, making sure that they stay separate without clumping together. 

To finish your look, Susannah recommends the Rimmel Kate Sculpting Palette in Coral Glow, £6.99 (http://bit.ly/2h9H4A5). The palette features a bronzer, blusher and highlighter. Susannah knows her bronzers (she never sets foot outside without one) and she really rates this one. The highlighter also works well to define cheekbones and high points of the face. The palette is perfect if your skin is a little lacklustre at this time of year, as it adds a beautiful glowy finish.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="108" average="4.81" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3456"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:qEYpRQJ8LJQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>qEYpRQJ8LJQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>What has landed on my desk this month (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qEYpRQJ8LJQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-11-29T16:26:22+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-01-11T01:51:38+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>What has landed on my desk this month (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qEYpRQJ8LJQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/qEYpRQJ8LJQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks us through the products that have landed on her desk this month that she really rates 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Using too many products recently has led to Susannah suffering from blemishes. The YSL Fusion Ink Cushion Foundation, £35 (http://bit.ly/2gC69QT) has been her saviour in terms of coverage as well as in evening out her base. This foundation has medium coverage, is easy to apply (with the sponge included) and lasts incredibly well.     

From the entrepreneur behind Soap and Glory, Marcia Kilgore, Soaper Duper is an ecologically sound collection of bath and body products. Susannah has enjoyed trialling it this month and is particularly impressed by its natural emollients, the great product sizes and price point. Susannah has been using the Soaper Duper Fruity Green Tuberose Body Wash, £7.50 (http://buff.ly/2gyGb3d) Soaper Duper Fruity Green Tuberose Body Lotion, £8.50 (http://buff.ly/2gyJnfm) and Soaper Duper Zesty Lemon Hand Cream, £6.00 (http://buff.ly/2fEQxdk). It is fruity scented without falling into the trap of being sickly. 

Susannah has been extremely excited about the Frederic Malle Portrait of a Lady Hair and Body Oil, £130 (http://buff.ly/2gbgBjY), which landed on her desk this month. Perfumier Frederic Malle is responsible for some of her favourite scents.  Portrait of a Lady is an iconic fragrance, with its rose, frankincense, cinnamon and patchouli notes and although the price point is high, Susannah recommends it especially if you are a fan of the original fragrance. 

After an unfortunate accident with a set of hair tongs, Susannah was left with a burn on her neck and has sworn by the 300-year-old Pommade Divine Nature’s Remedy Multi-Purpose Balm,  £19.80 (http://bit.ly/2gP2zWt) to get rid of it. The 97 per cent natural balm can be used for a multitude of purposes, including treating insect bites, cuts, grazes, eczema, psoriasis, scars, dry elbows, cracked feet as well as moisturising cuticles. Susannah notes that it has a beautiful cinnamon spice scent.

Finally, Susannah has loved using Hourglass Ambient Lighting Edit in Surreal Light, £69 (http://bit.ly/2gChu3m). This highlighter, blush and bronzer palette gives skin a natural glow, while at the same time preventing shine.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="94" average="4.91" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3752"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:bYSApXReqto</id>
  <yt:videoId>bYSApXReqto</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>My Pamper Routine (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bYSApXReqto"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-10-25T16:12:14+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-23T01:33:08+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>My Pamper Routine (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/bYSApXReqto?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/bYSApXReqto/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks us through her pampering regime and the go-to products to help her relax  

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Susannah loves having a bath and if she’s been doing a lot of exercise, her go-to addition to her bath is the BetterYou Magnesium Flakes, from £3.49 (http://buff.ly/2ejilWu). We are often deficient in magnesium and these flakes are a great way of helping get it back into the body though the skin. They also help to prevent muscle cramping by relaxing your muscles, while regenerating and repairing. 

In addition, Susannah loves a fragrant bath opting for Neom Lavender, Jasmine and Brazilian Rosewood Bath and Shower Oil, £40 (http://buff.ly/2e6n382) She either puts a capful into her bath or applies the oil directly on to her body before stepping into the bath. Another favourite is the Bamford Jasmine, Orange Blossom and Cedarwood Bath Oil, £40 (http://buff.ly/2e6mAmz) . 

After washing her hair, Susannah uses a hair mask and rates the Ojon Damage Reverse Restorative Hair Treatment, £19 (http://buff.ly/2e6qcF5). It is great for damaged or curly hair as the brand specialises in moisturising products for hair. Apply this mask throughout dry hair, leave the product on for 30 minutes and wash out. It restores and hydrates hair; Susannah notes that there’s nothing quite like it. 

Before applying a face mask, Susannah exfoliates her skin with the Aurelia Refine &amp; Polish Miracle Balm, £57 (http://buff.ly/2dRKrsd) to remove any debris or dry skin cells in order to allow the mask afterwards to work better. It contains small beads (not microbeads) that dissolve when rubbed into the skin. It’s incredibly natural and not at all harsh on the skin and it leaves skin ready for the next step. 

One of Susannah’s favourite face masks is the Sisley Black Rose Cream Mask, £95.50 (http://buff.ly/2eMNiAj) as it smells amazing, deeply hydrates, brightens and illuminates the skin. 

Susannah will then move on to the Leighton Denny Smooth Your Sole Foot File, £6 (http://buff.ly/2e6rmk0). One side will buff away any dead skin and the other side smoothes the skin. 

After the bath, Susannah’s go-to self-tanner is the Clarins Self Tanning Milky Lotion, £20 (http://buff.ly/2ejlOnI) as it provides a beautiful, non-streaky glowing bronze. It doesn’t have an unpleasant ‘biscuit’ fake tan smell as it uses fig extract. 

Before bed, Susannah applies the Elizabeth Arden Eight Hour Cream Nighttime Miracle Moisturiser, £32 (http://buff.ly/2eMOOmi) , which she feels is something of an unsung hero. It smells faintly of Eight Hour Cream and contains a slight lavender scent that relaxes. It’s a thick and smooth moisturiser and feels as though it is providing a protective layer for your skin while you sleep. In the morning you are left with super soft skin.  

Finally, to finish her pamper routine, Susannah will spray her pillow with the Neom Perfect Night’s Sleep Pillow Mist, £20 (http://buff.ly/2dRJqAG) containing lavender, camomile, jasmine and patchouli. It smells incredible and really helps her to drift off to sleep.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="96" average="4.79" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="5774"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:fBVqynCmnZ4</id>
  <yt:videoId>fBVqynCmnZ4</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Digital Detox: the art of switching off (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBVqynCmnZ4"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-10-18T15:21:04+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-25T15:29:10+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Digital Detox: the art of switching off (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/fBVqynCmnZ4?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/fBVqynCmnZ4/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor sets herself the challenge of a month-long digital detox – limiting her time on social media and keeping her phone out of the bedroom 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

As Editor-in-Chief of a website, Susannah is fully embedded in the digital world, but she has realised how crazy it has become.  She has increasingly felt the need to pull herself back a little from digital overload. We have all become completely addicted to our phones, she says, and she is no exception. 

The irony hasn’t escaped her that you’ll be reading this and watching her vlog on a digital device, but as Susannah notes, it’s important to take a step back - not to stop the use of technology, but to limit it. 

To complete her month-long experiment, Susannah will only be looking at her phone at specific times of the day. Checking Facebook is limited to once a day and Instagram once in the morning and once in the evening. 

Susannah had a wakeup call recently when she found herself walking down the street, checking Facebook on her phone. After looking up and taking in her surroundings, she realised that everyone else was doing the same, in their own little world, oblivious to others and even to the traffic as they crossed the road.  It dawned on her that she would take her phone everywhere (even to the loo!) and that something had to change. 

While Susannah encourages you to continue looking at Get The Gloss, she notes that enjoying digital media doesn’t mean being on our phones 24 hours a day. They don’t need to come with us to breakfast, lunch and dinner – and especially not to bed at night. 

Reading Thrive, the book by Arianna Huffington, co-founder and editor-in-chief of digital news site, the Huffington Post provided inspiration for Sus’s challenge. Arianna herself suffered from burnout and awoke one day on the floor of her office, having collapsed from exhaustion. 

Susannah believes overloading on social media can make us ill and advice posted there - especially on food and nutrition - doesn’t always come from qualified sources. Social media causes FOMO (fear of missing out) as we compare ourselves and to others, which can trigger anxiety and depression. 

Susannah likes Arianna’s idea of turning off notifications on our phones – putting ourselves in charge of our devices, not them in charge of us. 

Finally, she makes a plea for us to get back to living in the real world and to step away from the incessant digital chatter. 

If you’re with her in restricting your screen usage for a month, let us know!</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="68" average="4.82" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="1106"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:AlkuZlYxOAw</id>
  <yt:videoId>AlkuZlYxOAw</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Beauty Hacks (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlkuZlYxOAw"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-10-11T11:41:39+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-19T08:24:22+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Beauty Hacks (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/AlkuZlYxOAw?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i2.ytimg.com/vi/AlkuZlYxOAw/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks through the timesaving beauty hacks she can’t get enough of right now. 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Susannah dyes her eyebrows at home with the Colorsport 30 Day Brow Tint in Dark Brown, £8.25 (http://buff.ly/2deDYaC). No ‘slug-like’ brows here, with this at-home tint, Susannah can check the shade as she goes, saving time by not having to pencil them in afterwards. Plus it means no more regretted trips to the salon. 

To fill in brows further and keep them in place, Susannah’s go-to brow tamer is the Benefit Gimme Brow in Shade 1, £18.50 (http://buff.ly/2deD51O). This brow groomer adds a slight tint and sets brows into place – the fastest brow product she’s ever tried. 

Removing nail polish has never been so quick and easy. The Bourjois Magic Nail Polish Remover, £4.99 (http://buff.ly/2dZmug5) does away with the faff of finding cotton wool and the mess of removal, as the whole process takes place quickly within the pot.

Susannah’s final beauty hack is for hair. In her search achieve a natural beachy tousle at home, she called on Mel, a hair stylist from John Frieda for advice. Now she has finally found a no-fuss way get the look at home. After blow drying your hair smooth, pop your hair up into a top knot, twisting as you go (leaving the ends out to prevent unwanted kinks). Leave it for at least an hour, or overnight if you can and you’re left with a natural and textured beachy tousle without the need for tongs and products.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="139" average="4.94" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4168"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:kbm4if0l92g</id>
  <yt:videoId>kbm4if0l92g</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>What I’ve been using this month (Editor’s Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kbm4if0l92g"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-10-04T11:06:29+00:00</published>
  <updated>2016-12-09T10:48:39+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>What I’ve been using this month (Editor’s Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kbm4if0l92g?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i4.ytimg.com/vi/kbm4if0l92g/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks through the products she has been using and loving for the past month.

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

To help hydrate her unruly hair and restore condition after the summer, Susannah has been using the Charles Worthington Smooth &amp; Control range. The effect of the products is said to get better the more you use them – and while Susannah can’t vouch for that, she certainly loves the results so far. Her top pick from the range is the Charles Worthington Moisture Seal Hair Healer Leave-In Conditioner, £5.99 (http://buff.ly/2dNvFor) for its moisturising oils (argan, coconut and macadamia) and heat protecting properties. 

It’s not only Susannah’s hair that’s in need of a post-summer moisture boost - her skin is too. Her current favourite skin hydrator is the new Dior Hydra Life Jelly Sleeping Mask, £52 (http://buff.ly/2dAKzNq). Susannah’s skin has become noticeably drier since she turned 40 this year and she found that this gentle jelly, applied at night, left her with baby soft skin in the morning. 

This Works Perfect Legs Sculpt &amp; Shine, £28 (http://buff.ly/2dXlqx7) adds moisture and glow to legs at this time of year when we aren’t quite ready to fully cover up our legs. It is applied as a roll-on and has relaxing aromatherapy oils too. 

Unlike conventional deodorants, The Aurelia Botanical Cream Deodorant, £18 (http://buff.ly/2cPGX5K) takes the form of a pot of cream and is applied with the fingers. It contains no aluminium, commonly used to block pores in order to stop any smell or sweat. Instead, arrowroot and kaolin sit invisibly on the skin and absorb perspiration, while peppermint and eucalyptus oils counteract whiff-causing bacteria. 

Finally, Susannah has loved using the Dyson Supersonic Hair Dryer, £299.99 (http://buff.ly/2db2IOo) and although it’s super expensive, she feels it’s worth every penny. Revolutionising the hair dryer market, this new machine is lightweight, allowing you to get in all of the hard-to-reach places easily, while the nozzles snap magnetically onto the dryer and are structured to prevent heat damage. It’s compact and light and is perfect for travelling and is Susannah’s new go-to hair dryer.</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="84" average="4.62" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="3285"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:FVzfi0IbKGg</id>
  <yt:videoId>FVzfi0IbKGg</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>New in products: What's landed on my desk recently (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FVzfi0IbKGg"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-09-26T16:10:48+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-02-26T17:29:16+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>New in products: What's landed on my desk recently (Editor's Vlog) | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FVzfi0IbKGg?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i3.ytimg.com/vi/FVzfi0IbKGg/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>Editor-in-Chief Susannah Taylor talks through the products that have landed on her desk recently.

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Visit Get The Gloss for more beauty tutorial videos: http://www.getthegloss.com

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss

Skincare clinic Skin Laundry has arrived fresh from LA on a mission to improve our skin health. Founder Yen Reis suffered with skin issues that grew worse with age. Susannah can relate to that, as she’s currently experiencing breakouts. Yen’s speedy light and laser therapy treatment, which she discovered in Asia, is available at the new Skin Laundry store in Liberty London and Susannah can’t wait to try it. 

Alongside treatments, Skin Laundry also offers effective and targeted at-home beauty products. The Skin Laundry Nourishing Cleansing Oil, £24 (http://buff.ly/2cwkXNu) removes all makeup and impurities while softening and hydrating the skin.  The Skin Laundry Restoring Night Serum, £44 (http://buff.ly/2daX1Si) contains antioxidants, vitamins and peptides to reduce the signs of ageing.  But the product Susannah was the most excited about, however, is the Skin Laundry Sleep Cycle Clean Skin Pillowcase, £24 (http://buff.ly/2cwlDT0) which contains silver ion technology to help maintain cleaner and clearer skin while you sleep. 

The new self-tanning range from Tan-Luxe, available at Space NK is next on Susannah’s list as her current favourite for a natural tan. By adding a few drops of the Tan-Luxe Illuminating Serum Self Tan Facial Drops, £31 (http://buff.ly/2cWWi7E) or Tan-Luxe The Body Illuminating Self Tan Drops, £42 (http://buff.ly/2dtGKaE) into your daily moisturiser, you are left with a healthy bronzed glow without looking tango-ed. 

New from Sarah Chapman is the Skinesis Lash Boosting Eye Cleanse, £32 (http://buff.ly/2daYFU8). It’s an eye makeup remover that also works to lengthen your lashes. It contains biomimetic peptide hair care which will feed your lashes and help them to grow. With its no-fuss pump, it is incredibly easy to use.  

A new pillow mists on the market from Elle Macpherson’s WelleCo, the Sleep Welle Calming Mist, £24 (http://buff.ly/2dtK5pY) contains lavender, camomile and lemon extracts. This fine mist can be sprayed on to your pulse points or your pillows and its aromatherapy properties will help you drift off to sleep. 

There are so many liquid lipsticks on the market (Get The Gloss columnist Anna Hunter has examined the new trend (http://buff.ly/2cX1j01) but it’s the new YSL Vernis À Lèvres Vinyl Cream, £26 (http://bit.ly/2dcjnSq) that has caught Susannah’s eye. The glossy finish with its dense pigment sinks into your lips, leaving a balmy stain that lasts incredibly well. 

Finally, it has long been known that insects can be a great source of protein. Susannah puts this to the test by trying out the Jimini’s Baked Grasshoppers in Greek Spices and Paprika flavours (http://www.jiminis.com/) on camera. They might be high in protein, but do they score on taste? Watch Susannah’s vlog to find out…</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="124" average="4.52" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="4361"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <id>yt:video:lR3F826oeXQ</id>
  <yt:videoId>lR3F826oeXQ</yt:videoId>
  <yt:channelId>UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</yt:channelId>
  <title>Mary Greenwell: How to do evening makeup in your 50s | Get The Gloss</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lR3F826oeXQ"/>
  <author>
   <name>Get The Gloss</name>
   <uri>http://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLuJ8KZBypcoOHtZPoyEhw</uri>
  </author>
  <published>2016-08-04T15:15:28+00:00</published>
  <updated>2017-03-01T07:20:46+00:00</updated>
  <media:group>
   <media:title>Mary Greenwell: How to do evening makeup in your 50s | Get The Gloss</media:title>
   <media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/v/lR3F826oeXQ?version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" height="390"/>
   <media:thumbnail url="https://i1.ytimg.com/vi/lR3F826oeXQ/hqdefault.jpg" width="480" height="360"/>
   <media:description>We take your daytime makeup look straight through to the evening… 

Produced in partnership with Chanel. 

For the fourth in our series of videos with makeup artist Mary Greenwell, Mary answers the questions that you sent in. We loved your responses; many of you asked Mary to demonstrate evening makeup for women in their 50s. So here’s what she came up with… 

SUBSCRIBE now - http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=gettheglosstv

Where to find more from the editorial team and our experts at Get The Gloss:
ONLINE: http://www.getthegloss.com
TWITTER: http://twitter.com/GetTheGloss
FACEBOOK: http://www.facebook.com/GetTheGlossUK
INSTAGRAM: http://instagram.com/getthegloss
PINTEREST: https://uk.pinterest.com/getthegloss/
SNAPCHAT: https://www.snapchat.com/add/getthegloss 

Mary starts with the daytime look she created in our previous daytime makeup tutorial (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z1iFxM6KozI). First, she removes lipstick and applies the Chanel Hydra Beauty Nourishing Lip Care, £30 (http://bit.ly/2anHivR). This hydrates the lips while Mary focuses on the eyes.

To begin the eyes, she uses the same palette from the previous daytime tutorial (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z1iFxM6KozI) the Chanel Les 4 Ombres Multi-effects Quadra Eyeshadow in Tissé Vendome, £40 (http://buff.ly/1tjU8F0) and the Chanel Concealer Brush No.10, £21 (http://buff.ly/219XpB7). Mary applies the pale apricot shade under the brow bone as a highlight before applying the coral shade to the lid. Using the taupe shade Mary blends the shadow through the socket to make the eyes appear larger. 

Now on to eyeliner and Mary uses the Chanel Stylo Yeux Waterproof long-lasting eyeliner in Espresso, £19 (http://bit.ly/2azZLJ2) at the roots of the upper lashes, smudging it in with her fingers to open the eye. She then takes the dark shade from the Chanel Les 4 Ombres Multi-effects Quadra Eyeshadow in Tissé Vendome, £40 (http://buff.ly/1tjU8F0) palette with the Chanel Contour Shadow Brush No.14, £19 (http://buff.ly/2aRRTn0) under the eye and smudges it along the lash line to give a subtler eyeliner-esque look. The same shade is then applied into the outer corner of the eye to blend the liner and the shadows together to create a seamless eye look. 

For mascara, Mary uses the Le Volume Ultra Noir de Chanel in Noir Kôhl, £25 (http://bit.ly/2avJS4O) to thicken, build and volumise the lashes. 

On to the brows and Mary starts by feathering the Chanel Crayon Sourcils Sculpting Eyebrow Pencil in Blond Clair, £19 (http://bit.ly/2aWPWDI) back and forth through the brows to build a stronger brow. She then brushes the hairs through with the spoolie before using the next shade darker, the Chanel Crayon Sourcils Sculpting Eyebrow Pencil in Brun Naturel, £19 (http://bit.ly/2aWPWDI) to put a darker line through the middle. 

For the lips, Mary uses the Chanel Le Crayon Lèvres Precision Lip Definer in Natural, £17.50 (http://buff.ly/2aRVzVT) to fill in and make the lips look fuller before using the Chanel Rouge Coco Ultra Hydrating Lip Colour in Adrienne, £25 (http://bit.ly/2aCvqGP) straight from the bullet to give an extra bounce of colour without changing the look dramatically. 

To finish the look, Mary uses a small amount of the Chanel Poudres Universelle Natural Finish Pressed Powder in 20, £33 (http://buff.ly/1tjUQSH) around the nose and on the forehead, above the brows and on the chin, making sure to leave the natural glow across the cheeks. 
 
Credits:

Makeup by Mary Greenwell at Premier Hair and Makeup
Hair by Leigh Keates at Premier Hair and Makeup
Film by Mat Laroche at Chips Films
Model: Georgina Bartlett at Models 1
Model wears a Vintage Chanel top and Chanel ‘Comète Spirale’ earrings (J10814) 18K White Gold and Diamonds, £4,950</media:description>
   <media:community>
    <media:starRating count="618" average="4.98" min="1" max="5"/>
    <media:statistics views="26049"/>
   </media:community>
  </media:group>
 </entry>
</feed>
